Shuo Wang

0452298726 | jadesure17@gmail.com Melbourne CBD

WeChat: wangshuo869224943 | https://jadesure.github.io/ (personal blog)

Male

EDUCATION

Shanghai University of Engineering and Technology.

Sep 2012 - Jul 2016

Transportation (Aviation Equipment Maintenance). Undergraduate. Flight College

Shanghai

2012.09-2016.07 School scholarship 7 times (GPA: 3.2/4) 2014.09-2015.07 Outstanding student scholarship 3 times

RMIT University

Jul 2018 - Dec 2020

Information Technology (Master of IT). Master Sciences

Melbourne

GPA: 3.1/4

Related courses:

Information technology structure and security (IT Infrastructure and Security): It involves the IT introduction, maintenance, cloud service, network, security, etc. of each part of the computer hardware;

Internet of Things (IoT): Using Raspberry Pi: It involves hardware debugging, cloud service connection, etc;

Web Development Technique: Based on C#, Html, CSS, the bank transaction system runs through the front and back end with connecting the Azure database.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

China Eastern Airlines Co., Ltd. (Shanghai Science and Technology Aerospace Co., Ltd.).

Aug 2016 - Feb 2017

Shanghai

Aviation machinery maintenance trainee engineer. mechanical.

Civil aviation aircraft A320, A330, B737, B747, B777:

Maintenance of flaps, landing gear disassembly, engine replacement, hydraulic oil system, and control system.

AbsoluteSolution. Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

Electronic Equipment Repairer.

Melbourne

Assemble PC desktop computers, hardware equipment replacement, maintenance, and modular hardware troubleshooting; Install Window, macOS operating system, install various software, set up and debug;

Repair notebook software and hardware problems, such as electronic equipment stained with water, can not reboot the system, and hardware damage;

Install a firewall for the Internet cafes to avoid network attack;

Replace iphone6s, 6splus screen, battery.

PERSONAL PROFILE

I love electronic products very much, have great enthusiasm and interest in various electronic devices, and be proficient in operating windows, macOS, Linux. The individual holds a windows desktop computer with three monitors, MacBook pro, raspberry pi, windows laptop, iPad with apple pencil. Have strong learning ability and adaptability, work hard and carefully.

All the above internship experience can provide photos, work certificates, etc. as evidence